<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dallas Tour App</string>
    <string name="tab_restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="tab_shopping">Shopping</string>
    <string name="tab_concerts">Concerts</string>
    <string name="tab_sightseeing">Sightseeing</string>
    <string name="photo_desc_text">Thumbnail photo</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %$1d</string>
    <string name="dallas">Dallas</string>
    <string name="fort_worth">Fort Worth</string>
    <string name="parker">Parker</string>


    <!-- TAB restaurant and explanations !-->
    <string name="restau_truck_yard">Truck Yard</string>
    <string name="truck_yard_expl">Nothing describes Dallas to its essence as a beer garden.
        Truck yard is all that and more.A perfect no fuss come-as-you-are adult playground.
        Its great if you want to have a great time with locales and enjoy the outdoors while having
        a good time.It is also kid friendly.</string>
    <string name="restau_pecan_lodge">Pecan Lodge</string>
    <string name="pecan_lodge_expl">Texas bbq at its finest.Expect a line for sure, but service
        is super effective.Found in the hip neighborhood of Deep Ellum and, just a couple minutes
        from downtown  Dallas it is definitely worth the trip.You could always walk around the neighborhood
         and enjoy the other local businesses in the area.</string>
    <string name="restau_rodeo_goat">Rodeo Goat</string>
    <string name="rodeo_goat_expl">Best burger in the whole of Dallas.Ingredients are fresh  and they
        have hand punched fries.They
        got a wide selection of craft beers.If you visiting from out of town with your pets this
        place is perfect because it is also pet friendly.</string>
    <string name="restau_town_hearth">Town Hearth</string>
    <string name="town_hearth_expl">Swankiest steakhouse in Dallas with about 100 chandeliers and a
        Ducati parked in the restaurant.Super great vibe for a date night or just you want to want
        to experience a rustic vibe with a touch of glitz.Great menu with raw bar,steaks and classic
        cocktails.</string>

    <!--TAB Shopping and explanation !-->
    <string name="shop_galleria">Galleria</string>
    <string name="galleria_expl">Galleria is shopping mall located near Interstate 635 and
        Dallas North Tollway.It was originally developed by Hines Interests Limited Partnership
        in 1982.It has beautiful ice skating at the center of the mall which Olympic athletes and
        Olympic champions perform on once in a while.</string>
    <string name="shop_north_park_center">Northpark center</string>
    <string name="north_park_center_expl">It has more than 235 unique retailers, restaurants and
        department stores.It is located at the intersection of loop 12 and US 75.This mall offers an unparalleled luxury shopping experience.It was
        originally opened in 1965.</string>
    <string name="shop_dallas_farmer_market">Dallas farmer market</string>
    <string name="dallas_farmer_market_expl">Home to local vendors,merchants,artisans and craftmen
         of the area.It is located downtown Dallas.It opens 7 days a week but super fun to visit on weekends and ideal brunch
        location if you want to try a variety of local restaurants and food trucks.</string>
    <string name="shop_highland_park_village">Highland park village</string>
    <string name="highland_park_village_expl">An upscale shopping plaza located at the southwest
        corner of Mockingbird lane and Preston Road in Higland Park,Texas.It was also declared
        a National Historic landmark in 2000.It was the first self-contained shopping center in
        America.</string>

    <!--TAB concert ane explanations !-->
    <string name="con_winspear_opera_house">Winspear Opera House</string>
    <string name="winspear_opera_house_expl">Located in the Arts District of downtown Dallas, its a
         a 21st century reinterpretation of the traditional opera house.It is also one of the
         nations premier performing art venues.</string>
    <string name="con_granada_theater">Granada Theater</string>
    <string name="granada_theater_expl">A Dallas live music staple,it has been entertaining all ages
         in North Texas and everywhere else since 1946.It is located in Lower Greenville
         neighborhood  in Dallas.</string>
    <string name="con_the_rustic">The Rustic</string>
    <string name="the_rustic_expl">Located Uptown Dallas with great ambiance, it is prime spot if
        you want to enjoy live music from some popular bands.If you lucky during your vist you
        can catch a free concert too.</string>
    <string name="con_adair_saloon">Adair Saloon</string>
    <string name="adair_saloon_expl">Found in the neighborhood of Deep Ellum, its the perfect if you
         want to two step to some honky tonk.It is also know t be the best country music in the area.
         Do not forget to bring your cowboy hat and your boots.</string>

    <!-- TAB sightseeing and explanation !-->
    <string name="ss_jfk_museum">JFK museum</string>
    <string name="jfk_museum_expl">Found on the sixth floor at the Dealy Plaza which was formerly the
         Texas School Book Depository.It examines the life,times,death and legacy of President John
         F.Kennedy.It also located at the very spot from where President John F.Kennedy was shot by
         Lee Harvey Oswald. </string>
    <string name="ss_fort_worth_stockyards">Fort Worth Stockyards</string>
    <string name="fort_stock_stockyards_expl">The stockyards is a historic district in
        Fort Worth,Texas.The 98-acre portion encompassing much of the district was listed on the
        National Register of Historic places in 1976.</string>
    <string name="ss_south_fork_ranch">South fork ranch</string>
    <string name="south_fork_ranch_expl">A conference and event center in Parker,Texas.The ranch
        includes the Ewing Mansion which was the set for the television show Dallas.You can also
        have a guided tour of the ranch to see memorabilia from the series.</string>
    <string name="ss_dallas_museum_of_arts">Dallas museum of arts</string>
    <string name="dallas_museum_of_arts_expl">It is one of the largest art museums in America and
        located in the arts district of downtown Dallas.It was founded in 1903.Its growing
        collection contains one of the most important holdings of modern and contemporary art in
        the U.S.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
